

Zhao SongXun

Contact

Address ShenYang, LiaoNing, China

Phone +8615998333742

Email songxunzhao1991@gmail.com

Professional Summary

I am a full-stack developer with 7 years of experience.

I was hired by many clients and several startups including Producement, Live Bela LLC ,and Tranzport. In the previous company, Producement, I worked on several fintech projects using Java, Spring framework. I prefer working in an agile, fast-paced working environment remotely. because I believe autonomous, self-motivated, and fast-paced working is

because I believe autonomous, self-motivated, and fast-paced working is critical for a developer's career.

With solid knowledge and experience in PHP, Node.js, Python, HTML,

With solid knowledge and experience in PHP, Node.js, Python, HTML, CSS, Javascript, I always strive to produce a fully tested and efficient code based on perfect OOP design and strict coding style.

Now, I am interested in CI/CD using Github & Gitlab pipeline to various cloud platforms.

I can provide:

- Full-time work for 5 days per week
- Suggest new ideas and apply the latest technologies
- Real-time communication
- Lead development

My skills:

- .NET/C#, Python/Django & Flask, NodeJS/Koa, Loopback, MEAN, MERN stack, Mongoose, PHP/Laravel, Symphony,
- HTML, HTML5, CSS and various CSS architectures including SMACSS, BEM, OOCSS.
- Angular(any version), ReactJS, Nuxt, Vue.js, Next, Webpack, Babel, Javascript ES6
- Project Analysis
- Project Scheduling
- Test Automation
- Infrastructure Design

Work Experience

01/2021 - 04/2021

Ispolink

Frontend Developer

- Main tech stack: React, .NET, Docker, Jest, Metamask, Web3
- Worked as a sole frontend developer directly under CEO
- Developed various pages and components of the job portal
- Test-driven development
- The project passed Q2 ICO round and raised 2900K USD

11/2020 - 01/2021

Clean Kitchen

React Frontend Developer

- · Main tech stack: Shopify, React, Redux, Java, Spring
- Improved Shopify website for better conversion flow
- Reviewed commits and approve PRs
- Configure CI/CD pipeline

09/2020 - 10/2020

Salv

Full-Stack Developer

Main tech stack: Java, Spring framework, React

- Developed financial crime detection website
- · Worked as a full-stack developer

06/2020 - 08/2020

PayQin

Mobile App Developer

- · Main tech stack: Flutter framework.
- Reskinned existing PayQin mobile application based on the new framework.
- Worked as a full-stack developer, released PayQin mobile application.
- Solved GCP proxy problem

01/2020 - 05/2020

Estonia

Full-stack developer

- Developed Pactum chatbot
- Main tech stack: Java, Spring framework, React, Redux
- Worked as a full-stack developer, accepted by Walmart, raised 2 million USD
- Configuring OpenTelemetry and spring metrics

08/2018 - 10/2019

Entybox

Full-stack developer

- Main tech stack: Python, Django, Angular, Raspberry Pi, Java, Android, Github CI/CD
- Fixed bugs and improved performance of the legacy website
- Implement new design and features using Django + Angular stack
- Developed Raspberry Pi TV box

08/2017 - 08/2018

Live Bela LLC

Full-Stack Developer

Main tech stack: Python, Django, Angular, Heroku

- Launched Belacam photo-sharing website using Python + Angular Stack
- Delivered performance-driven and user-friendly website with better UI/UX design

06/2017 - 08/2017

Moonrock Consulting

Full-Stack Developer

- Main tech-stack: Node.js, VMWare VSphere, VMWare Firewall
- Utilized VSphere to run automation scripts
- · Launched firewall management website

01/2016 - 06/2017

Tranzport LLC

Backend Developer

- Developed API using Python + Django RESTful framework
- Delivered mobile application backed by API service

04/2015 - 01/2016

Play TAGG Limited

Frontend Developer

- Main tech stack: Angular.js, HTML, CSS, D3.js
- Developed new features and fixed UI/UX bugs

• Implement new design

05/2014 - 04/2015

Spoilt Social TV

Full-Stack Developer

- Main tech stack: PHP, Angular.js
- Developed new features and fixed UI/UX bugs

Education

04/2008 - 04/2014

Tianjin University of Technology

Bachelor of Computer Science

- Studied computer science, speech recognition, digital signal processing
- Submitted thesis for Noise reduction in speech

Languages

English

Fluent

References

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/zhao-songxun-73a990203/

Github: https://github.com/songxunzhao

Stackoverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/6879870/songxunzhao